Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor (Elmer Ellsworth Brown) RG.3.0.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - Chase, Harry Woodburn (Chancellor of NYU, 1933-1951), 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry Building Committee: Minutes, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Chemistry Department and Laboratory: University Heights, 1912-1918 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1918-1929 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Christie, Dr. Francis A. (Meadville Theological School), 1915 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Box Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - City Clerical Personnel, Program for, 1915-1916 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - City Club of New York, 1918-1921 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Civic Club of New York, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Clapp, Edwin J. (Professor of Trade and Transportation), 1912-1916 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Clark, Walter E. (College of the City of New York), 1917 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - College Board of the Presbyterian Church, 1910-1918 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - College of the City of New York, 1918-1933 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - College Education, Value of, 1922-1925, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Collins, G. Rowland (Assistant, Dean, School of Commerce), 1926-1929 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Collins Scholarship, 1924, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Colorado, University of, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Columbia University, 1915-1932 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Columbia University: Teachers College, 1923-1931 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1913, 1916-1920 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1921-1930 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Commencement: Centennial, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Commerce, School of, 1912-1926 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Commerce, School of: Deanship File, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Commerce, School of: Deanship File, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Commerce, School of: Division of Public Affairs, 1912, 1916-1918 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Commerce, School of: Retailing, 1919-1927, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Commerce, School of: Wall Street Division, 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Commissioners of Education (U.S. and New York State), 1918 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Community Relations, 1914-1918 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Conference on College Presidents, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Conference on Research, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Conferences with Deans and Officers, 1911-1912 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Connell, Jasper S., 1915-1916 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Continuation Committee of the World Missionary Conference, 1915-1916 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cosmos Club, Washington D.C., 1916-1918 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Council of NYU, 1915-1918 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Council of NYU: Chancellor's Statement to, 1916-1919 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Council of NYU: Membership, 1913-1917 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Council of NYU: Recommendations from the Annual Report of 1901, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Council of NYU: Special Committee on Educational and Financial Policy, 1924-1931 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Council of NYU: Special Finance Committee: Correspondence, 1924-1926 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Council of NYU: Special Finance Committee: Minutes, 1924-1926 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Council of NYU: Special Finance Committee: Miscellaneous Material, 1924-1925, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Council of NYU: Special Finance Committee: Schedules, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Crossett, Major Frederick M. (President, Class of Secretaries of NYU), 1914-1918 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1911-1913 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Damico, A.G., 1915 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Danton, George H. (Professor of German), 1920-1927 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Joseph B., 1923 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Day and Klauder (Architects), 1915-1932 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Deans and University Officers, Committee of, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Deanship of Women, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Deems Lectureship, 1917-1933 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Deems Lectureship: David S. Cairns, 1920-1924 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Deems Lectureship: Henry Churchill King, 1916, 1920-1924 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Deems Lectureship: James Moffatt, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Deems Lectureship: William D. Mackenzie, 1922-1933 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Deems Lectureship: Filmer S.C. Northrup, 1927-1928 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Deems Lectureship: Programs, 1922-1936 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - DeForest, Robert W., 1921-1933 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Degrees Conferred, 1917-1931, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Delamarre, Dr. Louis (Secretary General, Federation de L'Alliance Francaise), 1915 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Demarest, William H.S. (President, Rutgers University), 1913-1916 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1902-1925 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1926-1928 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1928-1931 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Department Store Education Association, 1915-1918 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Organization, Committee on, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Plans: Circular Letter and Replies, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Development and Promotion, 1912-1929, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Devoe Gift, 1919-1921 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DeWitt, Benjamin (Assistant to the Chancellor), 1915-1917 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - DeWitt Clinton High School, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - DeZafra, Carlos (Professor of Mechanical Engineering), 1916-1928 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Distler, Theodore A. (Secretary, Committee on Relations with Preparatory Schools), 1923-1933 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dix, William, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Downing, Augustus (University of the State of New York, State Department of Education), 1912-1926 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Draper, John W. (Professor, Department of Surgery), 1915-1917, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Drinker, Henry Sturgis (President, Lehigh University), 1916 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - DuBois, W.E.B., 1925-1926 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - DuPont, Coleman (Member, NYU Council), 1920-1925 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Dykar, Moses: Bust of Elmer E. Brown, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Eagleton, Clyde (Professor of Government), 1927 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Eastman, George (Eastman Kodak Company), 1922-1931 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Edison, Thomas Alva, 1920-1921 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Edmondson, Thomas W. (Secretary of the Faculty, University College), 1916-1917 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Education, School of, 1898-1933 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of: Deanship, 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Education for Americanization, 1917-1918 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Egan, Maurice Francis (Former U.S. Minister to Denmark), 1914-1924 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Egmont, Westy (International Law Research Institute), 1931 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Eliot, Charles W. (President, Harvard University), 1920-1926 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Engineering Fund Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Engineering, College of, 1918-1932 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Eno, Amos F.: Last Will and Testament, 1915-1917 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Erwin, J.W., 1916-1917, 1931-1933 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee of the Council of NYU, 1910-1926 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Extension Division, 1928-1930, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Extramural Division, 1914-1918 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Extramural Division: Advisory Committee, Wall Street Branch, 1913-1915 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Extramural Travel Courses, 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Fackenthal, Frank D. (Secretary, Albert Kahn Foundation), 1929 1932 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Club, 1917-1920 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1908-1920 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Statistics, 1914-1932 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fairchild, Henry Pratt (Professor of Social Economy), 1920-1928 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fall, Frank A. (Bursar), 1911-1920 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ferris, Mrs. Morris P. (Mary Lanman Dow), 1919-1927 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fetherston, John Turney ( Commissioner of Street Cleaning, New York City), 1917-1918, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Finances: General University Campaign, 1915-1923 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Financial Statements, 1904-1932 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1922-1925 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1928-1929 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fine Arts, College of, 1933, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fine Arts, College of: Deanship, 1928-1930 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fine Arts, Summer School and Lecture Pamphlets, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Finlay, Mr. And Mrs. George I., 1914-1927 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Finley, John H. (Commissioner of Education, New York Times), 1915-1935 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fish, Hamilton (U.S. Congress), 1930-1931 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fisher, Mitchell S. (Debating team; President, NYU Menorah Society), 1923 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Willard C. (Professor, Graduate Division of Business Administration), 1920-1927 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Fletcher, Austin B. (Counselor of Law), 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Flexner, Abraham (Secretary, General Education Board), 1917-1932 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Foch (Marshall) Ceremony, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Students: Instruction for Admission, 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Fraternities and Societies, 1911-1928 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Freeman, Katharine, 1928-1935 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - French, Daniel Chester, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Freschi Ceremony, 1930-1931 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Friedsam, Colonel Michael, 1925-1931 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Fuller, H. deWolf (Editor, New York), 1926-1932 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Gary, Elbert Henry (Chairman, U.S Steel), 1912-1927 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - General Education Board, 1912-1931 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Gerstenberg, Charles W. (Secretary, School of Commerce), 1912-1924 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Gibbons, R. James, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Gifts: Donors and Recipients, 1915, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Goddard Plan Training School, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Gold, Conrad, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Goldman Band Concerts, 1925-1933 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Gould, Helen Miller (Mrs. Finley J. Shepard), 1912-1934 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Government House, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School, 1911-1931 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Graham-Mulhall, Sara, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Graves, Frank P. (New York State Commissioner of Education), 1921-1923, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Greacon, Thomas E., 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Green, William R. (Chairman, U.S. Congress, Joint Committee on Internal Revenue Taxation), 1927 (Box 27)
  - Greendlinger, Leo, 1927-1928 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Greenwich Building, 1922, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Grimes, Bertha L., 1912 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Guggenheim, Daniel, 1926-1930 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, 1925-1930 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Gunn, Rev. Alexander; Memorial Tablet, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Gymnasium, Advisory Committee on, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Gymnasium (Heights), Committee on, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Gymnasium Dedication, Committee on, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Hall of Fame, 1914-1919 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Hall of Fame, 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Hall of Fame, 1922-1931 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Documents and Reports, 1900-1915 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1910, 1920-1921 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia, 1921-1932, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Hane, Alfred H. (Assistant Supervisor of Property), 1925-1928 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Haney, James Parton, Memorial, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Haney, Lewis H. (Professor of Economics and Director, Bureau of Business Research), 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Harriman, Mrs. Edward Roland, 1929-1932 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Haskins and Sells, 1918-1924 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Haubiel, Charles (Professor of Music), 1925, 1931-1932 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Havana, University of, 1929-1930 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Heaton, Harry C. (Professor of Romance Languages and Literature), 1920-1932 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Heckscher, August (Chairman, National Housing Committee for Congested Areas), 1926-1932 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Hendershot, W. Raymond (Bursar), 1925-1932 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Hepburn, A. Barton (Chairman, Advisory Board, Chase Manhattan Bank), 1919-1923 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Hering, Daniel W. (Professor of Physics), 1915-1932 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Higbie, Robert W. (University of the State of New York, State Department of Education), 1926, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education, Notes for the Study of, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Hill, Arthur E. (Professor of Chemistry, Havemeyer Chemical Laboratory), 1918-1933 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Hochfelder, Anna and Julius, 1926-1927 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hodenpyl, Margaret H., 1930-1931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Hodgdon, Daniel R. (Principle, Columbus School), 1928-1930 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Hodges, Charles (Professor of Government), 1923-1933 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1915-1920 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Hook, Sidney (Professor of Philosophy), 1930-1932 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Hoover, Herbert (President of the United States), 1920-1932 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Horne, Herman H. (Professor of Philosophy of Education), 1912-1933 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Hoskins, W. Horace (Dean, New York State Veterinary College), 1918-1921 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Hotchkiss, George B. (Professor of Marketing and Advertising), 1912-1933 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Hubbard, John C. (Professor of Physics), 1919-1933 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Huntington, Archer M. (President, Hispanic Society of America), 1922-1930 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Huntington, Henry E., 1920-1927 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Illinois, University of, 1918-1929 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Illinois State Normal University, 1921, 1930-1932 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Illustrated Booklets, 1921-1926, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Immigration Act of 1924, 1923-1928 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Indian Affairs, 1923-1926 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ingram, Federick F., 1922-1923 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Institute de Droit, International Luncheon, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Business, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Educational Travel, 1913-1915 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Institute of International Education, 1922-1933 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Institute of International Education: Printed Materials, 1925-1930 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Musical Art, 1906, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Politics, 1920-1924, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Interchurch World Movement, 1919-1920 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Intercollegiate Employment Bureau, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Intercollegiate Menorah Society, 1922-1923 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Intercollegiate Prohibition Association, 1925, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - International Affairs, Education in, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - International Correspondence School, 1924, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - International Exposition of American Import Trade, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - International House, 1924-1931 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - International Serbian Educational Committee, 1920-1927 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Irvine, Frank W., 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Irwin, John V., 1912-1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Italian American Society: Visiting Lecturers, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Iturralde, Maximo (Circula Literario Hispano de Nueva York), 1913 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Holmes C. (Professor of Physiology; Assistant Dean, Medical School; Dean, Dental School), 1925-1927 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Jefferson, Charles E. (Minister, Broadway Tabernacle Church), 1919-1925, 1932-1934 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Jenkins, Helen Hartley, 1910, 1921-1928 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple (Professor of Political Economy and Politics), 1911-1921 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple, 1922-1929 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple: Addresses and Lecturers, 1921-1927 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - John Price Jones Corporation, 1919-1932 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Joseph French (Dean, School of Commerce), 1913, 1916-1925 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (Director, Hall of Fame), 1918-1923 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1925-1927 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1928-1929 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1930-1933, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Johnston,W. Dawson, 1923-1928 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Joint Amnesty Committee, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Theodore F. (Professor of History, Director of the Gould Memorial Library), 1915-1935 undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Thomas Jesse (U.S. Bureau of Education, Phelps-Stokes Fund), 1916-1930 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Judaism: Hebrew University, American Friend of, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Judaism: Miscellaneous, 1922-1933 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Judaism: Oken Case, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Judaism: Pamphlets, 1920-1927, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Judaism: Yeshiva College Building Fund, 1925-1926 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Judaism: Zionist Organization of America and Hebrew University, 1917-1919, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Jusserand, Jean Jules (French Ambassador), 1923, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Kahn, Otto, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Kahn, Albert, Fellowship, 1925-1930 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kalbach, L. A. (U.S. Bureau of Education), 1912-1931 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Kalibala, Ernest, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Kellogg, Frank B. (U. S. Secretary of State), 1922-1930 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Kendall, James C. (Dean, Graduate School), 1927-1928 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, Emma Baker, 1913-1933 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Kenneson, Thaddeorus D. (Professor of Law) and Lucie C. Kenneson (Mrs. T.D.), 1918-1930 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Keyes, Charles H. (President, Skidmore College), 1920-1925 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Kilduff, Edwin J. (Professor of Business English), 1916-1933 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Kilmer, Annie Kilburn, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Kimball, Fiske (University Architect), 1923-1932 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Kimball, Leroy E. (Comptroller), 1909-1923 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Kimball, Leroy E., 1924-1927 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Kimball, Leroy E., 1928-1935 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - King, Arthur M., 1924-1931 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Klemin, Alexander (Professor, Daniel Guggenheim School of Aeronautics), 1923-1933 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Knapp, Harold C. (Trust Officer, Coal and Iron National Bank), 1925-1931 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Knighthood of Youth, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Knopf, S. Adolphus, 1920-1928 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Kohl, Clayton C., 1915-1917 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Kunz, Dr. George F. (President, Museums of the Peaceful Arts), 1915-1931 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lafayette College: Centennial Celebration, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - LaGarde, Paul, 1927 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Langdon, Russell C. (Professor of Military Science and Tactics), 1927-1928 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Lassman, Alfred, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Latin American Scholarships, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Law, School of, 1912-1931 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Law, School of: Actions of the Executive Committee of the Council, 1932-1942 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - League for National Unity, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - League of Nations, 1917-1931 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - League of Women's Organizations, 1923-1927 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - League to Enforce Peace, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - League to Enforce Peace, 1918-1919 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Ivy, 1923-1933 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lee, James Melvin (Director, Department of Journalism), 1916-1926 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lee, James Melvin, 1927-1930 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lefevre, Egbert (Dean, University and Bellevue Medical College, 1914-1915 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Lewishohn, Adolph, 1915-1929 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Liautard, Alexandre, 1918 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Loan Committee, 1917-1918 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Libraries, Council Committee on, 1933-1935 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Libraries, Statistics of the, 1929-1934 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Libraries, Union Catalogue of NYU (Boardman Collection), 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Library, University Heights (Gould Memorial Library), 1912-1922 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Library, Washington Square, 1921-1932 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Library Building, Washington Square (Proposed), 1929 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Library Committee, Chancellor's Joint (Washington Square), 1927 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Library Committee, Washington Square, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Library Survey, 1929-1934 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Library War Council for Greater New York, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Limouze, Arthur Henry (Minister, Northminster Presbyterian Church), 1920-1931 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Lipton, Sir Thomas J., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Litchfield, Edward Hubbard, 1920-1922, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Literary Digest, 1919-1929 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Littauer, Lucius N., 1926-1930 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Lomax, Paul (Professor of Commercial Education), 1925-1933 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Longfellow Society, 1916-1917 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Loomis, Milton E. (Registrar), 1915-1919 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Loomis, Milton E., 1920-1923 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Loomis, Milton E., 1924-1929 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Loomis, Milton E. (Dean of School of Education), 1930-1933 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Lopp, William (U.S. Bureau of Education), 1921-1934 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Lott, James H. (Manager, NYU Commons and Bookstore), 1922-1933 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Lough, James E. (Director, Summer School), 1912-1918 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Louvain, University of: Gifts to the Library, 1930-1931 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Louvain, University of: NYU Committee to Raise Funds for the Rebuilding of the Library, 1922-1923 1927 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Ly, Usang (President, Chiao-Tung University, Shanghai), 1930-1934 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - McAfee, Rev. Cleland B. (Minister, Lafayette Avenue Presbyterian Church; Member of the Council), 1912-1931 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - McClung, Reid (Glee Club), 1925-1927 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - McCollum, Dudley F. (Professor of History), 1927-1928 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - McCombs, Nelson W. (Librarian, Washington Square), 1923-1950 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - MacCracken, George Greer, Fund, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell (Chancellor Emeritus; Committee on the Hall of Fame), 1912-1918 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell: Dictionary of American Biography, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - MacCracken, Henry Mitchell: Memorial Service, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble (President, Vassar College), 1919-1925, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - MacCracken, Mrs. Henry Noble, 1924-1925 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - MacCracken, John H. (President, Lafayette College), 1911-1930 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - MacCracken Memorial Volume, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - MacCracken Property, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - McDonald, Philip B. (Professor of English, College of Engineering), 1922-1932 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - MacDougall, Robert (Professor of Education), 1916, 1927-1931 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - McElroy, Robert W. (Commencement Speaker), 1932 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - McEwen, Dean Currier, 1932-1933 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - McGehee, William H. O., 1932-1933 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - McIntyre, Judge Joseph F., 1918 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - MacKay, Clarence H., 1928-1930 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - McKim, Mead & White (Architects), 1925-1931 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - MacLean, Eda (Mrs. Joseph T.), 1921-1934 (Box 40, Folder 16)